react2media.com 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains how we use personal information, as defined below, and to give you assurance of our commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of your privacy as you visit and use this website (the “Website”). By using this Website, you accept and agree to this Privacy Policy, as well as the provisions of our [Terms and Conditions](https://clickperks.com/termsandconditions.htm). Please read all of our disclosures, terms and policies carefully before you agree thereto.

“Company,” “we,” “us” and “our” mean the operator of this Website, as well as its affiliates. “You” means the person or persons who use or submit information on this Website.

We understand that you value your privacy and the right to control how your personal information is collected and used. Our data collection and retention practices are designed to provide transparency, accountability and choice regarding the management and use of your personal information.

We also provide you with contact information should you wish to remove your personal information from our databases.

The Website is intended for users who are located in the United States of America and the Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States. By submitting information on/via the Website, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use, and transfer of your information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities under the law.

Please carefully review our Privacy Policy in full. If you do not agree to our practices, please do not interact in any manner whatsoever with the Website or submit any personally identifiable information on this Website.

Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy. You can reach us via postal mail at the following address:

React2Media 35 West 36th Street, Suite 4E New York, NY 10018

Any disputes relating to this Privacy Policy or Company’s handling of your information are subject to this Privacy Policy as well as this Website’s Terms and Conditions, including a mandatory arbitration provision and limitations on damages. Please review the Terms and Conditions carefully.

THIS WEBSITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR ANYONE UNDER THE AGE OF EIGHTEEN (18) OR PERSONS RESIDING OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA. BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU EXPRESSLY REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.

### 1\. Types of Information We Collect.

When you register for products/services made available via the Website, we collect certain personal information. Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify, locate, or contact an individual. The personally identifiable information that we collect may include, but is not limited to: first and last name, complete mailing address, email address, telephone number (including mobile telephone number), gender and date of birth, and such other information that we may request from time to time (collectively referred to herein as “PII”).

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information (“NPII”) about you when you visit many of the pages of this Website. This NPII includes, without limitation, the type of browser or device that you use, your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device ID referrer data, browser and platform type, the type of operating system that you use and/or the domain name of your Internet service provider. An IP address is a unique identifier that a device uses to identify and communicate with on the Internet. You do not have to register on the Website or provide any PII to us before we can collect this information. 

### 2\. How Your Information is Used and Shared.

We value your privacy and have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with relevant legislation, including, without limitation, the California Online Privacy Protection Act.

You agree that the information submitted by you on this Website will be shared, either directly or through intermediary agents and/or entities (including, lead aggregators and vendors to such businesses), with one or more third-parties, such as service/product providers, ad servers, advertising networks, marketers and/or affiliate companies (collectively, including intermediary entities, “third-parties”). Your information may be verified or supplemented with additional information obtained from other sources.

We may utilize PII and/or NPII obtained about you when you visit the Website, register for products/services made available via the Website, and/or information we obtain from third-parties, in order to provide you with and/or facilitate the third-party provision of targeted advertising solicitations and/or for analytical and audit purposes.

We do not take applications or make credit decisions. We do not control and are not responsible for the actions of any third-party. We are a marketing lead generator and advertising referral service. We do not charge you any fee. Third-parties have the option to purchase a given lead from us.

The selection of a third-party to acquire your information may be determined by a comparison of your information with available products/services. Company possesses a material financial connection to third-parties, in that we are compensated for each potential referral/sale.

Following submission of your information, you may be redirected to a third-party website and/or contacted by us or a third-party. We do not endorse any third-party. Third-parties may have their own terms, conditions and policies. Always carefully review all terms and policies. This service and offer are void where prohibited. Exclusions, limitation and conditions may apply.

Please carefully consider that third-parties may retain or use your information even if you do not use their services or obtain applicable products/services, and you should contact the third-parties directly concerning their privacy policies, which may differ from this Privacy Policy.

Your PII and NPII may also be used to send you first-party and third-party promotional materials. As such, Company and/or third-parties with whom your information may be shared, may target advertising to you by using direct mail, email, SMS text, telemarketing calls, targeted online banner advertising, applications and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

Company and/or third-parties that either serve advertisements on our behalf and/or on behalf of others may also use technology information to match your information to make and improve profiles of you, to track your online browsing habits over time and across different websites on the Internet, to show you targeted advertising for products and/or services, and/or to determine which areas of the Internet are most frequently visited.

Company may also use your information for data verification purposes, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot technical problems, enforce our agreements with you and to enable Company and/or third-parties to personalize your Internet experience.

Company may share your information with third-parties who help us in the delivery of the services you have requested and to companies/individuals we employ to perform technical functions on our behalf. These companies and individuals may not share that information with any other third-party or use that data for any other purpose.

Company reserves the right to append your PII from affiliated websites and/or third-parties in an effort to provide you with products and/or services you may be interested in. We may receive and supplement data we collect from/about you with information from third-parties. For example, if you are on a third-party website and you opt-in to receive information from us, the third-party may forward to us your electronic mail address and other data about you so that we may send you promotional messages. We may also supplement and combine the information we collect about you with outside records from third-parties in order to enhance our ability to provide you with promotional materials. Although applicable law may limit how such third-parties can use your information, we do not control the privacy practices of these third-parties. If you have any questions or wish to remove your information from a third-party’s database, you will need to contact that third-party directly.

By visiting and/or supplying your information at this Website, you agree to allow us to provide aggregated anonymous data about you to third-parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the Website and in order to offer you products and services. This includes demographic information and behavioral information. Company may disclose your information as permitted by law. We may also share, disclose and/or transfer the information we collect from you to a third-party who acquires any or all of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court.

We may disclose any/all information if legally required to do so, or at our discretion pursuant to a request from a governmental entity, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b) protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security; or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public. We may also use device identifiers to identify users, in our discretion. The foregoing may occur without notice,

Company encourages third-parties to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your information by third-parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control. 

**For more on how your information may be used by Company and/or third-parties, please see Section 3, below.**

YOU MAY OPT-OUT OF RECEIVING ANY PROMOTIONAL COMMUNICATIONS FROM US BY CHOOSING NOT TO SUBMIT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. IF YOU HAVE ALREADY SUBMITTED YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US AND WISH TO OPT-OUT AT A LATER DATE, YOU MAY DO SO BY WRITING US AT React2Media LLC, 35 West 36th Street Suite 4E. New York, NY 10018 BY CONTACTING US VIA EMAIL AT INFO@REACT2MEDIA.COM WITH THE SUBJECT LINE “UNSUBSCRIBE”, OR BY FOLLOWING THE INSTRUCTIONS IN THE COMMUNICATIONS THAT YOU RECEIVE. YOU MAY STILL CONTINUE TO RECEIVE TRANSACTIONAL/ADMINISTRATIVE NOTICES, AS NEEDED TO SERVICE YOUR ACCOUNT. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION BY THIRD-PARTIES IS GOVERNED BY THE PRIVACY POLICIES OF SUCH PARTIES AND IS NOT SUBJECT TO OUR CONTROL. IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS OR WISH TO REMOVE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM A THIRD-PARTY’S DATABASE, YOU WILL NEED TO REVIEW THE RELEVANT THIRD-PARTY PRIVACY POLICY AND CONTACT THAT THIRD-PARTY DIRECTLY.

### 3\. Email and Telemarketing.

By registering on and/or visiting this Website, you may also receive commercial email and/or telemarketing calls in response to your inquiry from Company or third-parties who receive your information as provided in this Privacy Policy. If you provide your express consent to receive calls or text messages, you may receive telemarketing calls or text messages at the phone number provided regarding products and/or services.

You expressly acknowledge that Company may provide your PII and/or NPII to third-parties for promotional offers by, without limitation, direct mail, email, telephone, mobile device and/or SMS text (including, your lawful prior express written consent in compliance with the E-SIGN Act, by automated telephone dialing and/or artificial pre-recorded voice) at the number provided. Company has captured information to prove prior written consent was obtained from you, via an electronic signature. Specifically, we may have captured an IP Address, website pages which contain the consent language and fields, associated screenshots of the consent webpage as seen by you where your telephone number was inputted, complete data record submitted by the you (with time and date stamp), or other identification sources. All collected information will be retained by the Company for a period of time as determined by the Company, which could be four years or longer.

Separate lists may be maintained for different purposes. If you wish to end your inclusion in a particular list, you need only to follow the instructions at the end of each communication to unsubscribe from the particular list.

By submitting your personal information to Company, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 C.F.R. § 310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the “ATSR”) and applicable state do-not-call regulations. As such, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, Company and/or third-parties receiving your information as provided herein retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR and applicable state do-not-call regulations. Where you provide “prior express written consent” within the meaning of the Telephone Consumer Protection Act (47 U.S.C. § 227), and its implementing regulations adopted by the Federal Communications Commission (47 C.F.R. § 64.1200), as amended from time-to-time (the “TCPA”), you consent to receive telephone calls, including artificial voice calls, pre-recorded messages and/or calls (including SMS text messages) delivered via automated technology, to the telephone number(s) that you provided. You are not required to consent to such telemarketing as a condition of purchasing any property, goods or services; you may revoke such consent at any time. Standard text message rates will apply.

PLEASE BE ADVISED THAT BY AGREEING TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU ARE OBLIGATED TO IMMEDIATELY INFORM US IF AND WHEN THE TELEPHONE NUMBER ASSOCIATED WITH YOUR MOBILE DEVICE(S) HAS/HAVE CHANGED.

Company is not responsible for third-party promotional communications sent to you. Company provides you the opportunity to “opt-out” of having your information used for certain purposes. You may remove your information from our database by contacting us directly. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be disclosed to third-parties or used by us to send promotional communications to you. In order to be removed from the databases of third-parties and to stop receiving direct marketing solicitation communications from them, you must review the relevant third-party privacy policy and contact that third-party directly. However, Company may retain information necessary to establish your lawful consent to receive marketing messages, and third-parties may retain information they have received from us. If you do not desire to receive further telephone communications from a third-party you have a right to request that you be put on its Do-Not-Call list. 

### 4\. Cookies, Web Beacons, Pixel Tags, Log Files, Extensions and Online Behavioral Technologies.

The Website and email messages may contain first-party (Company-related) and third-party cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, browser analysis tools and web server logs that enable Company and/or third-parties to track your online behavior, collect information regarding your operating system and browser/device type, record what webpage or email you viewed, track the IP address of the device you use to interact with the applicable online service, record when you open or click on a particular online advertisement link or webpage, and additionally for other information gathering purposes such as the language your system uses and the country and time zone of your device.

We may allow third-party ad servers or advertising networks to compile information about you and display promotional materials on the Website based upon your interests and use of independent websites. Third-parties may utilize persistent cookies or other similar technology that permit them to identify your computer or mobile device each time you are sent promotional materials. As set forth elsewhere herein, we do not have access to or control over the privacy or data collection practices of third-parties, and we may purchase or sell your PII and/or NPII to third-parties for marketing purposes.

A cookie is a small file uniquely assigned to you by a webpage server when you visit a webpage or click on a link and can assist in associating your information to a unique profile. Cookies are stored in web server logs and also in web cookies kept on your computer, which are then transmitted back to us and/or third-parties by your computer. Information about your account, preferences, your use of the Website and your online browsing habits may be stored. Such information allows us and/or third-parties to recognize you when you return, and track and target your interests in order to provide a customized experience. They also assist with the detection of certain kinds of fraud.

Some cookies are temporary, whereas others may be configured to last longer. “Session” cookies are temporary cookies used for various reasons, such as to manage page views. Your browser usually erases session cookies once you exit your browser. “Persistent” cookies are more permanent cookies that are stored on your computer even beyond when you exit your browser. Your browser preferences may be capable of being modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set.

Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on website pages or in emails that allow Company and/or third-parties to determine whether you have performed specific actions. When you access these pages or open email messages, the pixel tags and web beacons generate a notice of that action. These tools permit the measurement of responses to communications and improve related promotions.

We may assign an ID number to your registration and link additional data to that ID number, such as the date and time you visited, the information you provide and the links you choose to click. Like most standard website servers, we use log files to collect and store this user information. Log files include IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer a website, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We may analyze and use this information for a variety of purposes, including operating and improving the Website, collecting further information about and learning from user behavior and trends, and gathering demographic information.

Furthermore, we may combine or link information we collect from or about you offline with information we collect from or about you online through the Website. You may choose to install and use optional browser extensions, add-ons or similar plug-in technologies that may also collect and use your information in a variety of ways. Please note that third-party affiliate or advertising network cookies, or other similar technologies, may be placed on your computer when you install and use an extension or when you click on an affiliate or advertising network link, your browsing activity on our partners’ websites (and, with consent, other websites) may be tracked, and that information may be shared with third-parties, including advertisers, intermediary agents and/or entities (including, lead aggregators and vendors to such businesses), service/product providers, ad servers, advertising networks, marketers and/or affiliate companies, or others to provide you with advertising, content, surveys, offers, promotions, and rewards, or for other marketing, administrative and general business purposes.

As set forth herein, Company and/or third-parties collect many different types of information from cookies and other technologies, including, without limitation, what website you were visiting before you came to the Website, the website you visit after you leave the Website, and other activities of yours over time and across third-party websites and online services.

As applicable, the use of cookies by third-parties on the Website and in email messages is subject to the privacy policies of these third-parties and is not covered by this Privacy Policy.

Third-parties that place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or non-human readable identifier corresponding to your email address to a web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No PII is on, or is connected to, these cookies.

We may also use geo-location technologies to determine the city and/or geo-coordinates of where you are located, including whether you are using a mobile device. We may use and share such information with third-parties in order to provide you with promotional content, based on your location. Please note that our mobile applications may collect, among other things, certain information automatically, including, but not limited to the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique device identifier, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, your mobile Internet browser and data pertaining to the nature of your mobile application use.

We do not have access to or control of such technologies that may be placed by third-party ad servers or third-party advertising networks. Third-party advertising networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt-out of ad targeting. 

### 5\. Managing Your Privacy.

As set forth herein above, Company and/or third-parties that either serve advertisements on our behalf and/or on behalf of others may use technology information to match your information to make and improve profiles of you, to track your online browsing habits over time and across different websites on the Internet and to show you targeted advertising for products and/or services.

Because an industry-standard Do-Not-Track protocol has not yet been established, Company's information collection practices will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy regardless of any “Do Not Track” signals that may be sent by certain browsers or selected by you. However, you can visit www.cookiecentral.com and www.aboutads.info to learn more about this type of advertising and how to opt-out from receiving it by from companies that participate in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) self-regulatory program. Opting-out, however, will not stop advertising from appearing on your browser. Rather, it may make the advertisements that you are presented with less relevant to your own personal interests.

We believe that you benefit from a more personalized experience when we know more about you and what you like. However, you can limit the information you provide to us and thereby limit the communications that we and/or third-parties send to you.

To prevent first and third-party online tracking from cookies, web beacons and other technologies on a webpage, website, or within an email message, for example, banner advertisements, do not visit the Website, utilize a changing IP address and do not click on or interact with any advertisements or links. Visit cookiecentral.com and aboutads.info to read more about cookies, including, without limitation, how you can modify your browser preferences to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is sent (for example, from within Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome). As each browser is different, please check the help section of your browser for instructions on how to remove cookies and learn about other privacy and security settings that may be available.

To prevent first and third-party online tracking from cookies, web beacons and other technologies within an email message, unsubscribe from the email list using the unsubscribe link provided. 

### 6\. Security of Your Personally Identifiable Information.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information we gather online, Company stores your PII in a database on secure systems. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial security procedures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to PII. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information, to the extent reasonably possible. Employees who do not adhere to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action.

But notwithstanding such measures, Company cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent Company computers from being illegally accessed, and the data on them stolen or altered, and Company assumes no responsibility for such actions. You may request that your information be modified or deleted, as detailed herein.

In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your PII. Third-parties who receive your information are obligated by contract and/or applicable law to also protect your PII. However, Company is not responsible for the conduct of the third-parties and does not warrant or guarantee the quality of their efforts, if any, to protect your information. 

### 7\. No Information Collected From Children.

Company encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. We will never knowingly collect any PII about children under the age of eighteen (18) years old. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected PII about a child under the age of eighteen (18) years old, that information will be immediately deleted from our database.

Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third-parties. Company has also designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”). 

### 8\. Links to Other Websites and Third-Party Privacy Practices.

Company may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may have their own privacy statements in place. We are not responsible for the content of linked websites or any use of such websites. Whether linked or not, you expressly acknowledge that other websites and/or websites of third-parties have their own privacy statements and personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy statements provided by any/all third-party websites prior to providing them with information or taking advantage of an offer or promotion.

### 9\. Special Notification for California Residents.

As a business subject to California Civil Code section 1798.83, Company must disclose, upon request, the identity of third-parties to whom Company has disclosed your PII within the previous calendar year, along with the categories of personal information disclosed, for the third-parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, you may communicate your desire to do by contacting Company here, or via mail at React2Media LLC, 35 West 36th Street Suite 4E. New York NY 10018 We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the contact information specified above.

### 10\. Changes to This Privacy Policy.

Company reserves the right to change or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notification. If Company changes this Privacy Policy, updates will be posted herein. Information will be used in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner.

Please check the Website frequently to apprise yourself of any changes that may affect you. The posting of any changes will be the only notice that you will receive regarding any such amendments or changes. 

### 11\. Privacy Inquiries or Complaints.

Company strives to keep all PII accurate and complete. You are always fully in control of the information that we maintain to service you. You can also request that PII be deleted, however, Company reserves the right to retain information necessary to establish lawful marketing consent. Information may also be withheld or exempted from deletion if this is required by law or is part of a fraud investigation.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information we gather online, we store your personally identifiable information in a database on secure systems. We have put in place physical, electronic and managerial security procedures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

If you have any inquiries regarding our privacy practices, believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy, or would like to access and modify your PII, please contact us, please review our Privacy Policy or contact us via email at info@react2media.com or by writing to us at:

React2Media LLC  
35 West 36th Street, Suite 4E  
New York, NY 10018

California residents may also file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs via mail at 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814 or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210 or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.

EFFECTIVE: 5/18/2017
